

Ukraine, Kyiv+38 096 29 37 844

☑ shev950@gmail.com

s join.skype.com/invite/e4FfRTYuxdSO

in linkedin.com/in/shevchenkolha

About me

I'm Front End Developer with 3+ years of experience since 2019. My core programming languages are JavaScript and TypeScript. I love to build modern web apps using OOP, SOLID, and the Angular framework. I always work on personal growth and my skills improvement.

Languages

English - B2.

Work experience

Front End Developer

July 2020 - Present

Digicode (Kyiv, Ukraine)

Projects: LotteryHeroes, KayaMoola, Flybet, Supabets, GoldRush, Gbets, 10Bets, Backoffice

Period: September 2020 - Present

Description: SPA provides the chance to engage in the big lottery draws and engage in a diverse selection of non-lottery games to instantly win prizes. Built on Angular version 12.

Responsibilities:

Feature development: this involves creating new Angular components, services, directives, or other Angular elements to implement new features in the application.

Refactoring and improving existing code: improving code quality, ensuring adherence to coding standards, and fixing architectural or design issues.

Bug fixing: identifying and fixing bugs in the frontend part of the application, which may involve analyzing stack traces, debugging, and testing fixes.

Performance optimization: enhancing the performance of the frontend part of the application, optimizing page load times, and caching data or resources.

Redesign: implementing new UI design, and creating new SCSS functions, mixins, and vars.

Backend interaction: developing or integrating the frontend part with backend APIs, processing received data, and displaying it on the interface.

Testing: writing and executing tests to verify the functionality of new features, identifying and fixing bugs.

Documentation: writing code documentation, describing new features, and providing instructions on using components or services.

Code reviews: actively participating in code reviews as both an author and a reviewer to identify issues, address shortcomings, and improve overall code quality.

Researching new technologies and tools: Learning and implementing new tools, libraries, or frameworks that could improve front-end development.

Used technologies: JavaScript, Angular 4-12, TypeScript, OOP, SOLID, NgRx, RxJS, Unit Testing, Web Socket, SSR, ECMAScript, Git, HTML5, SCSS, Bootstrap 4, Flexbox, BEM.

Project: Lenders & Members

Period: February 2021 - October 2021

Description: SPA for purchasing and registration of cars in the USA. Built on Angular version 9.

Used technologies: JavaScript, Angular 9, TypeScript, OOP, SOLID, RxJS, ECMAScript, Git, GitFlow, HTML5, SCSS, Bootstrap 4, Flexbox, BEM.

Project: BMM Comply

Period: July 2021 - September 2021

Description: SPA related to slot machines and audit. Built on Angular version 9.

Used technologies: JavaScript, Angular, TypeScript, OOP, SOLID, Angular Material, RxJS, ECMAScript, Git, GitFlow,

HTML5, SCSS, Bootstrap 4, Flexbox, BEM.

Project: Sorbet

Period: May 2021 - June 2021

Description: Landing page for Sorbet marketing company. Built on jQuery.

Used technologies: JavaScript, jQuery, AJAX, Git, GitFlow, HTML5, SCSS, Bootstrap 4, Flexbox, BEM, Perfect-Pixel.

Project: Digicode Internship **Period:** July 2021 - August 2021

Description: Landing page for Digicode Internship program. Built on jQuery.

Used technologies: JavaScript, jQuery, AJAX, Git, GitFlow, HTML5, SCSS, Bootstrap 4, Flexbox, BEM, Perfect-Pixel.

Project: Gemsoft

Period: July 2020 - September 2020

Description: Corporate website for games developer company. Built on NextJS.

Used technologies: JavaScript, Next.js, TypeScript, OOP, SOLID, Git, GitFlow, HTML5, SCSS, Bootstrap 4, Flexbox,

BEM, Perfect-Pixel.

HTML coder

February 2019 - February 2020

Imrev, (Khmelnytskyi, Ukraine)

Responsive web design and enhancement of existing websites of varying complexity.

Skills ————	
JavaScript	
Angular	
TypeScript	
NgRx	
RxJS	
Unit Testing	
ООР	
SOLID	
HTML5	



Education

A2Lab

October 2018 - December 2018

Courses about HTML & CSS, Basic JavaScript.

